Gourav Dhamecha

WEB DESIGNER / DEVELOPER

As a web Designer/developer, my objective is to make a positive impact on clients, co-workers, and the internet using my skills and experience to design compelling and attractive websites using Mysql, JAVA, and PHP, I Energetic Web Designer/Developer with 3.6 years of experience creating and maintaining the functional, attractive and responsive website for companies.

WORK EXPERIENCE



GRAPHIC'S WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER

Vrtti Consultants.Pvt.Ltd - a tech firm that specializes in providing a range of online services to users February 2022 to Present (02 + years)

- Maintained a user satisfaction rating by providing responsive tech support to clients.
- Working on providing productivity by creating a website to organize, track bugs, and add feature requests
- Achieved Learning about new / using various programming languages by using a number of websites.
- Maintaining client data and client Website backup files & and checking the Website Regularly based on website bugs and problems and fixing them.



GRAPHIC'S WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER

Freelancer world - all types of services like logos, banners, brochures, flyers, pamphlet website design, website Development, working on improving the website or maintaining of website, redesigning a website.

September 2021 to Febuaray 2022 (6 months)

- Working According to the client's demand for ex: creating logos, designing pamphlets/brochures/ prospectus, defining modules, etc.
- Improving clients' websites according to their needs and creating new websites for them.



WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER

Planet media Center - August 2020 to August 2021 (01 years)

• Solving code Problems format designs, texts, and media for use in print and web applications.



gouravdhamecha2001@gmail.com

+91-844-701-4129

Nawada, New Delhi, Delhi-110059, India

Click here for my portfolio

EDUCATION HISTORY



BACHELOR OF COMMERCE B.com.

DU SOL School of Open Learning, University of Delhi, India



CERTIFICATIONS

February/2021 - Web Designing *at SitHub.in*

• June/2020 - Graphics/ Web

Designing & Development at Network

Educations

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Java, HTML, XHTML, CSS, jQuery, PHP, SQL, Bootstrap, MYSQL, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, CorlDrow SQL, WordPress, Google Analytics, WordPress.
- Front End & Back End Coding.
- · Technical Documentation
- Knowledge of Facebook ads, Facebook ads manager, React.js, Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe Animator, Adobe XD, Figma, Social media Marketing, C++ and Python.

EXPERTIES

 Web Development, coding and programming, Cross-Browser Compatibility, site troubleshooting, UX & UI Design, Search Engine Optimization, Hosting and Maintenance, Digital & e-commerce Strategy, CRM & CMS Platform, information architecture, multimedia Design.



- Editing & Design with designing team in the company to build perfect web designs.
- Design websites for various businesses.
- Daily maintenance of existing sites and applications.
- •Creating a backup files created logo prototypes and processed publication-ready advertisements.
- Creating qraphics elements such as logos , banners, button etc.
- Applications/framework Design as needed.

PERSONALITY

- Communicative
- Creativity

LANGUAGES

- Hindi
- English

SKILLS

- Oral and written Communications
- · Committed to Lifelong Learning
- · Team Building
- · Reliable and Consistent
- Creativity
- Positivity

Tip: Add a company logo for brand recognition. Link its website or profile to its name. You may also add a short description of what the company does.